Hi.
你好呀
I specialize in the field of Learning Science,
我专注于学习科学领域
and I'm excited to share strategies on best learning habits.
很高兴能分享最佳学习习惯的策略
Before we get started,
在我们开始之前
these strategies are proven effective ways to learn
这些策略被证明是非常有效的学习方法
new material and have been extensively researched in fields of Learning Science,
并在学习科学领域得到非常广泛的研究
Neuroscience and Cognitive Psychology.
如神经科学与认知心理学
I use these strategies as I learned programming,
在我学习编程的时候 我运用了这些策略
and I love sharing these with everyone I meet.
我喜欢和我遇到的每个人分享我的发现
Your time is valuable.
你的时间非常宝贵
So it is important that the time you spend learning is used in the most effective ways.
因此 以最高效的方式来学习非常重要
Here are some ways you can do that.
以下是一些方法
Lesson 1. Space your learning.
第一课 学习空间
To remember or retain what you have learned,
为了记住你所学习的内容
space out your learning sessions.
你需要周期性空出一段时间
Since you're spending five hours on,
你学习了5个小时了
say, Saturday and Sunday,
比如说 周六和周日
spend two hours at least five days over a week.
一周至少5天每天花费2个小时
Even having shorter review sessions of 15-20 minutes a
即使是15-20分钟的快速回顾
few times a week will go a long way in retaining that information.
每周几次快速回顾将帮助你更好地记忆
This habit allows you to review the same material
这个习惯会帮助你反复回顾同一份学习材料
repeatedly and makes the neural pathway in your brain stronger.
并锻炼你的大脑和记忆力
An Intern helps you recall the concept when
当你被问到复杂的问题的时候
you're asked complex questions about it which,
这个习惯可以帮助你快速记忆起相关的概念
come to think of it, is quite programming and data science are all about.
这会帮助你学习编程和数据科学
Lesson 2. Write notes.
第二课 记笔记
Don't type your notes.
不要用键盘输入你的笔记
Study show that writing those notes out about
研究表明 手写下笔记的内容
new learning material is more effective
会更加高效
for long-term learning than typing out your notes.
这将有助于长期的学习 而不是用键盘输入
There are few reasons for this.
这里有一些原因
As you write your notes,
当你在输入笔记的时候
you're making more connections between your visual and motor systems in the brain.
你大脑中的视觉和运动系统之间建立了更多的联系
Also, writing is a slower process than typing,
而写字是一个比打字更慢的过程
but it forces the deeper processing of the information.
它促使你对信息进行更深入地处理
Keep in mind, I'm not talking about verbatim writing what the speaker is saying,
请记住 这里不是在谈论如何逐字记录演讲者所说的话
but instead pausing, reflecting on what you heard and then writing notes.
而是停顿、反思你所听到的内容 然后写下笔记
This deeper processing of information is more
更深入地处理信息可以帮助你更有效地
effective for later applying that information in complex ways.
面对之后可能面对的复杂问题
If you want to type the notes,
如果你想输入笔记
reflect on what you're learning and then type it out.
也需要反思所学习的内容 然后再输入
Lesson 3. Spend time recalling, not recognizing.
第三课 花一些时间回忆 而不是辨识
Recognizing is remembering something after you see a cue.
辨识是指在看到一些提示之后 你可以回忆起所学的内容
Recalling is remembering something at will, without a cue.
回忆是指在没有提示的情况下 随意地记住所学的东西
So when you're ready to review previous concepts,
所以当你准备好要复习以往学习的概念的时候
close your notebook, and force yourself to recall or remember the information.
关闭你的笔记本 并强迫自己回忆或记住这些信息
Don't just read your notes.
而不是仅仅去阅读你的笔记
This makes the neural pathway stronger because you're forcing your brain to meet
这会使得你的大脑神经更强壮
that neural connection to remember
因为你在促使它们之间相互连接
the concepts against existing mental models in your memory.
以记住你心中所想的那些知识点概念
I use this method often, for example,
我经常使用这个方法 举个例子
to remember the sequence of coding statements for typical coding assignments.
在一些常见的编程任务中 为了记住一些代码语句的序列
Also, I do it frequently in environments that are outside my usual study space.
我经常在我平时学习空间之外的环境中这么做
For example, when I'm washing the dishes or when I'm walking the dog.
举个例子 当我在洗碗或者遛狗的时候
So, try it out.
所以 试一试
Lesson 4. Connect concepts.
第四课 连接知识点
When making notes, think about how different concepts
在做笔记的时候 想一想不同的知识点是否可以组合在一起
fit together or connected and are different from each other.
或者相互连接
These steps are all examples of deeper processing.
这些都是深入去理解和处理知识的例子
For instance, in programming,
比如说 在编程的时候
you will learn about various data containers.
你将学习各种数据容器
To connect the concepts,
为了连接这些知识点
you can think about how each of these are different from
你可以去思考每一种数据容器的差异和相似之处
each other and similar and when you would use each.
以及何时使用它们
By doing this, you're essentially making the network
这样的做法 实际上可以使得你大脑中的知识网络
of knowledge in your brain more dense and interconnected.
更加密集地联系在一起
So when you have to do more complex processing,
所以 当你要面对更复杂的处理的时候
you can see the pattern more easily.
你就能更容易地看到背后的特征和模式
Lesson 5. Mistakes are learning opportunities.
第五课 错误是学习的机会
Program requires a different way of thinking that you will
编程需要你运用一种不同的思维方式
need to get used to when learning it for the first time.
在第一次学习的时候 你需要习惯
Learning it will take time,
学习编程需要花费不少的时间
so be patient with yourself.
所以你也要对自己的消化理解保持耐心
As you encounter errors, review them.
遇到错误的时候 检查你的代码
Take the time to look at the code.
花些时间仔细查看你的代码
Add print statements to help you debug,
添加更多的打印语句可以帮助你调试
and then think through it.
然后仔细思考
Understand why they happen.
了解它们发生的原因
It will stick in your brain this way,
它就会牢牢地被你记在大脑中
and you will know what not to do next time.
下一次 你就会知道如何避免
Don't forget, you can also use Udacity's resources such as knowledge or slack,
不要忘记 多多使用 Udacity 的论坛等资源
to see how others figured it out.
看一看别人是如何解决这个问题的
I hope you will try out the strategies.
希望你能够尝试这些策略
We want you to succeed in this program and enjoy the learning process.
希望你能够在该课程中取得成功！详细学习的过程吧！